Guide to the Fay Chiang Papers TAM.748
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Fay Chiang Papers
1960-2017
1980-2017
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Chiang, Fay, 1952-2017
Chiang-Waren, Xian
TAM.748
21.66 Linear Feet in 37 manuscript boxes, 3 half manuscript boxes, 3 card boxes, 2 oversized folders, 1 flat box, 3 oversized flat boxes, 1 media box, and 1 CD box
5.6 Gigabytes in 123 computer files
7 videocassettes
Fay Chiang (1952-2017) was a poet, writer, visual artist, and activist. She was the director of Basement Workshop, an Asian American arts organization, and the author of numerous works spanning poetry, fiction, and non-fiction including In the City of Contradictions, Miwa's Song, and 7 Continents 9 Lives. In addition to her writings, Chiang also worked with numerous non-profit groups which combined cultural and educational work with community activism. The Fay Chiang Papers (1960-2017) consists of materials created and collected by Chiang documenting her writing career, involvement with various socio-political arts organizations including Basement Workshop, activism on behalf of Asian Americans, and some aspects of her personal life. Materials in this collection include photographs, personal correspondence, journals, notebooks, address books, project files for arts and community activism efforts, original drawings, administrative documents, and original writings in various formats and stages of completion. The collection also includes a small number of objects and video recordings.
Scope and Contents
The Fay Chiang Papers (1960-2017) consists of materials created and collected by Chiang documenting her writing career through both published and unpublished works; her involvement with the arts, political, social outreach, and literary organizations; activism on behalf of Asian Americans; and some apsects of her private life. Themes of Asian and Asian Americanness, art, politics, and her activism are overarching and intersecting themes represented throughout this collection.
The collection contains published copies of In the City of Contradictions, Miwa's Song, and 7 Continents 9 Lives; manuscript drafts of these books, some with revisions; correspondence with her editors about the publication of these books; Chiang's notes about these works; and transcripts of interviews about her written works. Chiang's poetry was also featured in issues of the Mom's Egg Review (MER), a literary art journal about motherhood, and Bowery Women: Poems, a collection of poems written and published by the Bowery Poetry Club in New York City. In addition to published works, the collection contains copies of individual poems such as "Orchard Street" and "Chinatown"; original plays such as Two Boots and a Ball Gown and Laundryman; drafts of her writings and unfinished pieces; and research materials and handwritten notes with her ideas. In her handwritten diaries and journals, Chiang documented her daily life, her inner thoughts, ideas for written pieces, and sometimes drawings. Both Chiang's published and unpublished works span poetry, fictional essays, plays, and non-fiction articles, all of which reflect topics that were of interest to the author. In addition to Chiang's published works, the collection contains several commercially published books written by other individuals that either discuss Fay Chiang or contain personlized messages to her.
Recorded readings of Chiang's books In the City of Contradictions and Miwa's Song, as well as audio and video interviews of Chiang discussing her career as a writer, are included in the collection.
Fay Chiang was affiliated with various organizations throughout her life including Basement Workshop, Poets and Writers, Project Reach, and Zero Capital. Materials related to these organizations include correspondence and memoranda; program flyers and event advertisements; photographs and posters; handwritten notes; administrative papers including budgets, membership rosters, grant applications, and funding paperwork; original artwork and writings; organization publications and newsletters; and mission statements. Together, these documents provide an overview of Chiang's activities with each organization, while also demonstrating her continued commitment to social justice, community building and outreach, and art.
Chiang was diagnosed with breast cancer in 1994 and received continued medical treatment until her death in 2017. Chiang discusses the long-term impact this illness had on her and her family's life, as well as her daily struggles living with cancer in various poems and essays found in this collection.
Finally, the collection includes family photographs, some of which are in the form of born-digital files and scrapbooks; personal correspondence; journals, notebooks, and agenda books; address books; and some personal ephemera, such as her high school yearbook, awards, and mixed music CDs from friends – all of which provide insight into Chiang's personal life and some details about her family.
Arrangement
The materials in the collection are arranged in a single file listing with all material listed alphabetically by topic.
Conditions Governing Access
All journals and diaries, housed in Boxes 19-31, are restricted until January 1, 2098. All incoming and outgoing correspondence written during the period of between January 1, 1988 and January 1, 2017, including letters and printed-out emails, is restricted until January 1, 2047. Certain materials may be released prior to January 1, 2047 with written permission of the donor. This correspondence is housed in Boxes 31-38.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Xian Chiang-Waren in April and September 2018, and March 2020; the accession numbers associated with this gift are 2018.104, 2018.112, 2019.083, and 2020.021.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access to some audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room.
Audiovisual materials that have not been preserved may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Born-Digital Access Policies and Procedures
An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Biographical Note
Fay Chiang (1952-2017) was a poet, writer, visual artist, and activist. She was a first-generation Chinese American raised in Jackson Heights, Queens and she spent much of her life in the East Village. Chiang was the author of numerous works spanning poetry, fiction, and non-fiction including In the City of Contradictions, Miwa's Song, and 7 Continents 9 Lives. In addition to her own writings, Chiang was active within New York City's literary community and was part of Poets and Writers. Poets and Writers, founded in 1970, is a nonprofit organization focused on providing support, fostering professional development, and creating a literary community amongst creative writers. Chiang served as the organization's president from 1998-2000. She worked closely with its Writers Exchange (WEX) Program, which was established in 1984. It was the WEX program's goal to introduce emerging writers to specific literary communities. Chiang also worked closely with Poets and Writers' literary readings and workshop community outreach programs.
Chiang also worked with numerous non-profit groups whiuch combined cultural and educational work with community activism. She was the director of Basement Workshop between 1975-1986, an Asian American political and artistic organization founded in New York City's Chinatown. Basement Workshop existed between 1970 to 1986 and was focused upon community service, education programs, and trying to reconcile Asian and Asian American cultural identities. Basement Workshop organized workshops, published magazines and newsletters, and hosted various performances. Chiang was also involved with Project Reach, a substance abuse prevention and anti-discrimination training group for all ages, genders, and races, and Zero Capital, a collective of international artists, activists, and youths collaborating together on social and political projects.
Chiang was diagnosed with breast cancer in 1994 and received continued medical treatment until her death in 2017.
Separated Materials
At the time of processing, two copies of Generasian Magazine (NYU - Asian American Student Affairs magazine) were transfered to New York University's University Archives and added to New York University Archives Collection of Publications and Ephemera (MC.334).
Asian Americans.; Asian Americans -- Ethnic identity.; American poetry -- Asian American authors; Chinese Americans -- New York (State) -- New York.; Asian Americans -- Politics and government.; Artists.; Chinatown (New York, N.Y.); Photographs.; Plays (performed works); Books.; Diaries; Correspondence.; Journals.; Printed ephemera.; New York (N.Y.).; VHS; Administrative reports; Chiang-Waren, Xian
- 3rd Annual Asian/Asian American Jazz and Cultural Festival, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 3rd Annual NYC Asian American Studies Conference, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
- 7 Continents 9 Lives - Announcement of Book Publication, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 7 Continents 9 Lives - Biographical Note, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 7 Continents 9 Lives - Drafts, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 6-9, Box 2, Box 3, Folder 1-6)
- 7 Continents 9 Lives - Press, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- 19th Asian Pacific American Heritage Festival, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Activist Imagination (Kearny Street Workshop), 2008 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Address Books and Rolodexes, circa 1994-2015, undated (Box 4, Folder 3-5, Box 41)
- Afternoon Shower Performance Photos (Ohio Theater, Soho), 1983 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Agendas and Calendars [RESTRICTED], 1995-2014 (Box 19, Box 20)
- Alliance of New York State Arts Organizations, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Alliance of New York State Arts Organizations -- Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1998 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Amerasia Journal, Vol. 3 No. 1, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- America's Many Voices Performance, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Amious Curiae: The Execution of Chung-Yi Miao, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Apicha Community Health Center, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Artist in Residence Grant - Jean Chiang, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Asian American Arts Design (Magazine of the Asian American Arts Alliance), 2001 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Asian American Leadership Conference (Yale University), 2009 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Asian American Organizations, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Asian Pacific Americans in Higher Education Conference (APAHE), 2002 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Asian/Pacific/American (A/P/A) Institute (New York Univerisity), 1997, 2003-2006 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Asian/Pacific/American (A/P/A) Institute (New York Univerisity) - AIR Welcome Event: Fay Chiang, 2003 (Box 39, Vhs 748.0004-748.0005)
- Asian/Pacific/American (A/P/A) Institute (New York Univerisity) - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 2005 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Asian Pacific Islander American (APIA) Spoken Word and Poetry Summit, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Asian Tactical Theater, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Award - Conference on Chinese American History, NYU, 1999 (Box 40)
- Basement Workshop, 1976-1986,1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Basement Workshop - Anniversary, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Basement Workshop - Arts Initiative: A Legacy Project of Basement Workshop, 2016-2017 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Basement Workshop - Basement Yearbook, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Basement Workshop - Charlie Chin and Fay Chiang Photographs, 1976, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Basement Workshop - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 2016 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Basement Workshop - Godzilla: Asian American Arts Network Exhibit at New Museum, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 11, Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 1)
- Basement Workshop - "Hiroshige's Eagle" (paintings by Fay Chiang), 1977 (Flat-file-folder 9, Folder 9)
- Basement Workshop - Interview Transcript with East Coast Asian American Student Union (ECAASU), 2008 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Basement Workshop - Interview Transcript with Fay Chiang and Yuh-jen Lu, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Basement Workshop - Race and Culture in Nonprofits: The Transformation of New York Asian American arts organizations, 1971-2004 (Bo-Seon Shim), 2006 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Bob Avakian, 2007 (Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 2)
- Book List, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Boricua College - Women Writers Poetry Series, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Bowery Poetry Club, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Bowery Women Poems, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- A Capitalist Meltdown of the Global Kind (Poetry by Regie Cabico), 2009 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Chee Chin, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- The Chinese of America, 1785-1980 (Him Mark Lai, Joe Huang, Don Wang) (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Chinese-American Planning Council, 2015-2016 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Conference Materials, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Correspondence - Bo Seon Shim [RESTRICTED], 2004, 2013 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Correspondence - Condolence Cards (Fay Chiang's Death) [RESTRICTED], 2017 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Correspondence - Condolence Cards (Fay Chiang's Mother's Death) [RESTRICTED], 1999 (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
- Correspondence - Ding Kong [RESTRICTED], 2000, 2007-2011 (Box 32, Folder 3-6, Box 33, Folder 1-3)
- Correspondence - Don Kao [RESTRICTED], 2002, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Correspondence - EFA (Elizabeth Foundation for the Arts) Project Space [RESTRICTED], 2015 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Correspondence - Fay Chiang to Oprah Winfrey [RESTRICTED], 2011 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Correspondence - General, 1967-1987 (Box 6, Folder 7-11, Box 7, Box Shared Tamiment 169, Folder 3)
- Correspondence - General [RESTRICTED], 1988-2017 (Box 33, Folder 7-8, Box 34, Box 35, Folder 1-2)
- Correspondence - HOWL Poetry Reading [RESTRICTED], 2011 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Correspondence - Jack Tchen [RESTRICTED], 1998, 2003-2009 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Correspondence - Janine Pommy Vega [RESTRICTED], 1998 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Correspondence - Jean Chiang [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Correspondence - Mark Waren [RESTRICTED], 1996, 2007-2008 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Correspondence - Miki Akamatsu [RESTRICTED], 2004, 2009 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Correspondence about Mine Okubo [RESTRICTED], 1998-1999, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Correspondence - Mom Egg Review [RESTRICTED], 2008-2009 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Correspondence - New York City Asian Student Conference [RESTRICTED], 2009 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Correspondence - New York Newsday [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Correspondence - New York Poetry Festival [RESTRICTED], 2011 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Correspondence - The Poem Archive [RESTRICTED], 2013 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Correspondence - Poetry Festivals [RESTRICTED], 1998-1999 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Correspondence - Publishers [RESTRICTED], 1996, 2000-2015 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Correspondence - Richard Oyama [RESTRICTED], 1999-2007 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Correspondence - Rosemary, 1970-1971 (Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 3)
- Correspondence - Seoul International Writers Festival [RESTRICTED], 2012 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Correspondence - Siddhartha Joag [RESTRICTED], 2003-2011 (Box 36, Folder 11-13)
- Correspondence - Taiyo [RESTRICTED], 2003, 2005, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Correspondence - Teru [RESTRICTED], undated, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Design Festa Live Stage - Tokyo, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Diaries and Journals [RESTRICTED], 1982-2003 (Box 21, Box 22, Box 23, Box 24, Box 25)
- Diaries and Journals [RESTRICTED], 2003-2017, undated (Box 26, Box 27, Box 28, Box 29, Box 30, Box 31, Folder 1-6)
- East Coast Asian American Student Union (ECASU), Georgetown University, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- EFA (Elizabeth Foundation for the Arts) Project Space - "Speaking Portraits: A Conversation with Stolen Lives and Families", 2015 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Family Photographs, circa 1980s-2000s; cuid42572 (Box 8, Folder 4, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_748_ER_5)
- Fay Chiang Biographies, circa 1990s, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Fay Chiang's Business and Identification Cards, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Fay Chiang's High School Yearbook, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Fay Chiang's Resumes, undated; cuid42573 (Box 8, Folder 8, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_748_ER_10)
- A Gathering of the Tribes, No. 11, undated (Box 8, Folder 0)
- Guerilla Art, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Hunter College - Fay Chiang Undergraduate, 1969-1970, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 12, Box Shared Tamiment 169, Folder 4)
- Hunter College - Teaching, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Hypnagogic Review (Aleksandar Zograf), 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Icons of Presence: Asian American Activist Art (Leland Wong, Jim Dong, Nancy Ham), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- In the City of Contradictions, 1981, 2006, 2016; cuid42574 (Box 8, Folder 16, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_748_ER_2)
- In the City of Contradictions and Miwa's Song - Excerpts, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- In This Life - Drafts, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 1-5)
- In This Life - Manuscript, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Interviews, 2009; cuid42575 (Box 9, Folder 7, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_748_ER_4)
- Interviews - Fay Chiang, Bill Zimmerman, and Students from Philisophy 378 (Stony Brook University), 2004 (Box 39, Vhs 748.0007)
- Interviews - Fay Chiang and Doug Moy, 2004; cuid43205 (Box 39, Vhs 748.0001)
- Interviews - Fay Chiang, Margo Machida, and Taiyo Ebato, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Interviews - Fay Chiang and Srilata, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Interviews and Poetry Readings, 1988; cuid42580 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_748_ER_9)
- Janine Pommy Vega, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Japanese American Community Services - Cecelia Nakamura Arts Fund Application for Funding, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Karen Su, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Laundryman, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Ledwig House Writers Residency, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Louis Reyes Rivera LifetimeAchievement Award, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- The MacDowell Colony - Literature (Winter/Spring), 2014 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Mia Vita, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Mine Okubo, 2000-2003 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Mine Okubo - Citizen 13660, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Miwa's Song, 1982, 2006; cuid42576 (Box 11, Folder 1-2, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_748_ER_3)
- The Mom Egg Review, 2006-2017 (Box 11, Folder 3-9, Box 12, Folder 1)
- The Mom Egg Review - Fay Chiang Poems (Excerpts), 2006-2016 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Mott to Mulberry (Written & Directed by Herman Lew, features Fay Chiang), undated; cuid43056 (Box 39, Vhs 748.0002)
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Duration: 33 minutes
- Neighborhood Voices, undated (Box 39, Vhs 748.0003)
- New York Chinatown History Project, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- New York City Arts Coalition, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- New York Foundation for the Arts, 1997, 2007-2008 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- New York Foundation for the Arts - Art Fellowship, 2014 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- New York Foundation for the Arts - Writing Samples, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- New York Newsday, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
- New York Poetry Festival, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
- New York State Council for the Arts, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- New Work - Draft, 2015-2016 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Non Fiction Literature Work Sample Inventory, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
- The NuyorAsian Anthology - Asian American Writings About New York City (Bino A. Realyu), 1999 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Obon By the Hudson (Richard Oyama) - Draft, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Orchard Street Wellness and Advocacy Collective, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Ordinary Women, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 5-6)
- Original Art, undated (Box 13, Folder 7, Box Shared Tamiment 171, Folder 2)
- Original Art for Fay Chiang by Ding Kong, 2013 (Box Shared Tamiment 169, Folder 2)
- Original Art - Fay Chiang and Xian Chiang-Waren, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 175, Folder 1)
- Original Poetry, 1982-2016 (Box 13, Folder 8-10, Box 14, Folder 1-3, Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 4)
  Scope and Contents
  These folders contain copies of Fay Chiang's original poetry. Poems include: "Untitled," "Notes from Japan," "My Changing City," "What It Means to Be an American," "Song for Xian," "How Shall I End My Days," "Wind for Xian," "Diving," "Flight," "In the City of Contradictions," "Outside my Window," "Samuel," "Daughter for Xian," "Mrs. Oltrani," "Father II," "In This City for Taiyo," "A Strange Dream," "Change," "For Xian on her 27th Birthday," "Cold Duck and Beer in the Toilet Tank," "Moonrise," "Sonnet: Silence," "Autumn," "World," "Reinvention," "Kin for Dong," "Portraits," "Air," "Some Thoughts on the 1995 Budget Cuts," "Basketball," "Stories (Story #1)," "What Did My Mother Think of All of This (Story #2)," "Chinatown," "A Big Round Wooden Table," "Grandma," "Jya," "Mrs. Ho," "In Chiapas," "In the Dim Afternoon Light," "Orchard Street," "Mask," "Tall Grasses Rippling in Wind," and "Landmarks and Geography."
- PEN American Center, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Photographs of Fay Chiang, circa 1960s-2010s (Box 14, Folder 5-6)
- The Performance Piece- Newsletter of InsideOut, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Poems from Stage One of "All the Worlds Between", 2015 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- A Poet's Visit - Fay Chiang Reads, 1988 (Box 39, Vhs 748.0006)
- Poets and Writers - Administrative, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Poets and Writers - African American Initiative, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Poets and Writers - Asian American Philanthropy, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Poets and Writers - Budgets and Financial Documents, 1998-2000 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Poets and Writers - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1998-2004 (Box 37, Folder Unknown, Box 38, Folder 1)
- Poets and Writers - Correspondence -- Charles Simic Food Poetry [RESTRICTED], 1998 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Poets and Writers - Correspondence -- Fay Chiang's Appointment Letter [RESTRICTED], 1998 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Poets and Writers - Correspondence -- Fay Chiang's Resignation Letter [RESTRICTED], 2000 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Poets and Writers - Fay Chiang's Performance Review/Overview of Responsibilities, 1998-2000 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Poets and Writers - Focus (Newsletter), 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Poets and Writers - Focus Group on Audience Development, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Poets and Writers - Focus Group on Audience Development -- Correpondence [RESTRICTED], 1998 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Poets and Writers - Funding, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Poets and Writers - German Literary Houses, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Poets and Writers - Grants, 1998-2000 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Poets and Writers - "Growing the Literature for a Democracy", 1998 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Poets and Writers - List of Asian American Media Outlets, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Poets and Writers - Literary Events and Outreach Programs, 1997-1999, 2012 (Box 15, Folder 9-10, Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 5)
- Poets and Writers - Literary Events and Outreach Programs -- Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1998-1999 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Poets and Writers - Magazine, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 11)